Gran?
Kinoshita Nagomi
Speaker
Oh, Kazuya. About the
birthday party tomorrow...
I've been wondering if we
should order sushi or pizza.
What would you like?
Here we go again. Birthday party.
Every year on June 1st, my birthday,
the whole family eats together.
Happy 14th Birthday!
It's one of our iron-clad rules.
Volatile
teen
Happy birthday, Kazuya!
Volatile
teen
Sushi, I guess?
I knew you would say that.
Nagomi:
Same fr fr
You called me just for that?
Kazuya:
Where did you
even learn that?
Oh, one more thing.
When is Chizuru-san's birthday?
I couldn't do anything for her last
year since we'd only just met,
but I want to bring her legal
adulthood in with a bang this year!
Oh, actually, Chizuru's birthday
passed a while ago.
I don't believe you!
Eardrum
destroyed
shake
Why didn't you tell me?!
smack
Yep, saw it coming.
That's why I didn't
want to mention it.
I've ignored the birthday of the Kinoshita
heir's wife two years in a row!
Oh God...
Forgive me,
honey!!!!
I'm a failure as a grandmother and matriarch!
This shame will haunt us for generations!
She's not my wife! Slow down, will you?
That's it. We're having a
combined birthday party.
Combined? What?
Listen here, Kazuya.
Man up, talk to Chizuru-san, and bring her
to our place tomorrow, no matter what!
Not happening!
I'll make sure we give
her a princess's welcome.
Seriously, it ain't happening!
Kinoshita Nagomi
Nagomi Sake
LIVE Audio call ended
Gah! Kill me!
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"Kiss and Girlfriend"
There are no koi on my balcony.
Could you stop
throwing fish food?
Uh, that's a snakehead pellet.
It's not for koi.
I couldn't care less.
Are you free tomorrow night around five?
Is this about your grandmother?
Quick on the uptake!
It always is.
The thing is, it's my birthday tomorrow.
But when I told her yours was in April,
she insisted on throwing a
combined party for both of us.
Well, I did find it strange that
she didn't call me on the day.
R-Right on the money.
Sorry.
I'm going to see my grandmother
in the hospital tomorrow.
Th-The hospital?
She needs me there after her tests,
so we talked about it a while ago.
So five o'clock isn't happening.
Ah, okay...
I can't bother her and her grandma.
Gotcha. Sorry for asking.
I'll make up an excuse for Gran.
I wasn't done talking.
I can't do five, but I can make it there
after six. Keep her occupied until then.
R-Really?
I'm not doing this for you.
I'm supposed to be your "girlfriend"
until I quit this job.
Also, happy birthday.
Damn, she's cute.
Hum   Hum
Quit singing on cloud nine!
I'm causing her problems again!
Ruka-chan
LIVE Audio...
Reject
Answer
Huh? Ruka-chan?
Pop
Happy birthday!
And there goes
my left eardrum, too.
Huh? Kazuya-kun? You there?
Wh-What's up?
Giving you a birthday call at midnight sharp!
Just like any girlfriend would!
It's that late already?
Thanks...
I can't see you today, but I get
you all to myself on Sunday, right?
June 1
R-Right.
No! No!
She sure caused a scene when I told
her I couldn't see her the day of...
No! No!
My, my.
Oi, oi.
No!
Birthday date!
It's great that you're
so close to your family.
I don't have a problem with it as long
as Chizuru-san's not gonna be there.
Huh?
Wha?
Oh, shoot!
Wait, it's not what you're
thinking. My gran...
Ruka-chan
LIVE Audio call ended
I screwed up!
All | Missed calls
History
Ruka-chan(3)
LIVE Audio
Kinoshita Nagomi
Pizza Hot
Redialing
Does she know? Does she?!
Crap, she's not answering...
Guess I gotta make it up to her on Sunday.
All done.
Come, let's be on our
way to your family home!
Wh-Why are you here, Ruka-chan?
Well, I am your girlfriend.
I decided I had to attend your
family's birthday party, after all.
But we agreed to meet on Sunday.
Yes, we did.
Y-Yeah, she totally knows.
Her ribbon
looks like horns...!!
Sorry I didn't tell you.
Yeah, Mizuhara's coming tonight,
but that's only because my gran suddenly
decided to make it a combined party.
I wasn't trying to hide it from you...
Oh, is that so?
Welp, she's pissed.
Am I gonna survive this?
Here we are.
Wow, your place is huge!
Not really. We only live on the second floor.
We've rented out the third and fourth floors.
Ah, so you turned it into
an apartment building.
Yeah, though neither this nor
the store make much money.
C'mon, we can't be locking arms here.
Chizuru, my ang— Huh? Ruka-dono?
Hello!
Talk
about
a
false
start
Chizuru said she'd drop by later.
This was sudden, so she had other plans.
Oh, I see. Letting you in now.
It's too bad. But we didn't
exactly give her any warning,
so I'm thankful we managed
to work something out.
Yes,                                       yes
Anyway, glad to have you, Ruka-dono.
Come on in.
Thank you for having me.
My angel Chizuru will feel more
at ease with a friend around.
Wait, Kazuya. Line up your shoes.
I wanna be called "angel," too.
-dono
isn't cute
Chizuru-san
Kazuya, happy birthday!
Chizuru-san Love
What time did she say she'd be coming?
Around six, I think.
So much for celebrating my birthday.
And look at all that sushi!
DUN
They're not much, but please have these.
What?
For us?
It's the day your dear grandson was born.
It must be a special day for the family, too.
My! Thank you so much!
Wow, you're such a thoughtful young lady.
Who are you trying to fool?!
O-Okay, Ruka-chan, let me show you around.
You will?
Come on, Kazuya.
It's not like we live in a mansion.
Don't get her
hopes up.
It's fine. Get the drinks
served in the meantime.
So, this is the kitchen...
We good? We're good, right?!
Wha? What do you mean, "good"?
I mean our relationship!
My family still thinks
Mizuhara's my girlfriend.
You won't rat us out to Gran, will you?
You won't
rat us out,
right?!
Hold up! Rethink this!
You two aren't being fair!
You say your relationship's purely business,
but you were trying to spend your family
birthday party with her, without telling me!
Is there something I should know?
Again, I wasn't trying to hide it!
I'm your girlfriend, aren't I?
You just can't tell your grandmother the
truth about Chizuru-san 'cause she loves her.
Isn't that what you said to me?
Yeah, I sure did...
Then don't stop me from
trying to redeem myself!
Whoa, keep it down!
Yeah, yeah, you're right!
Without Chizuru-san here, this is my chance.
What are you saying?
I'll make sure your grandmother loves me!
Enjoy your birthday.
Itabashi Third Hospital
I'm going to go refill the flower vase.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
I'll be fine. Don't worry about me.
6 PM
Itabashi Ward, Ooyama Town
Sorry! And thanks!
Oh, a necktie?
Yes. I wanted Kazuya-san
to look more grown-up.
I see. Impressive, Ruka-dono.
It's both a funny and a practical gift.
Good for you, Kazuya.
Here you go, Father.
Ah, sorry about the foam.
It's fine.
Some birthday this is!
Without Mizuhara here,
m 0 0 l 130 0 l 130 250 l 0 250
Cute
grand-
daughter
act
I'm very good at massages, you know!
Ruka-chan really is going all-out
to create a favorable impression.
I'll take the drinks.
m 0 0 l 130 0 l 130 250 l 0 250
Capable
daughter
act
Oh, thank you.
Even in my eyes, she's playing
the ideal girlfriend.
And for you, Grandmother.
Is this sake?
And she's broken the ice
with them in just an hour!
Yes. It's called Junmai Daiginjo.
What's up with Mizuhara, though?
It's way past six.
Chizuru isn't here yet?
Kazuya, why don't you try calling her?
Huh? Call her?
O-Okay, I'm gonna step
outside for a sec, then.
Sure, run along!
Huh?
He knows her number?
Grr...
No, there's no way he'd have a
rental girlfriend's personal info.
Chizuru-san isn't here,
and he can't contact her!
This really is a golden opportunity!
Please, drink up!
She's gonna win over my family in no time.
Hurry up, Mizuhara...
Ichinose Chizuru
Notifications              Block              Add Friend
But I can't call her without
adding her as a friend.
They're hitting it off.
Call her!
Add Friend
Game over.
Adding her as a friend is too much for me.
Sorry, she didn't answer.
Guess she's busy.
Oh... I'm worried about her.
Check!
...is what it
feels like.
I'll try again later.
I just hope she's all right.
You know, I had no idea
Ruka-dono was such a nice, cheerful,
and responsible young lady!
I feel at home next to you, too.
My rook's in danger!
She's entering
the endgame!!
You kind of have the same scent
as my grandma in Hokkaido.
Oh, the countryside?
My parents and I would go visit once a year.
I loved my grandma and all the
different scents of Hokkaido...
But she died the year before last,
so I don't think I'll be going back.
Ruka-dono...
Ruka-san...
I have no idea if it's true or not!
But either way, it's working!
Ah. That must've been so hard.
You're always welcome here, okay?
Think of me as your Tokyo
grandma and rely on me.
What if you were to become my real grandma?
All right, time out!
Ow!
Kazuya!
Friend or not, you can't
cover a young lady's mouth!
It's beyond rude!
When did you
sink so low?
S-Sorry, but...
It's not
like that...!!
Ruka-dono, you were saying?
Shit, I can't stop her!
Who is it? This is not the time!
received a message from Ichinose Chi
is suspicious, please report
Today
Ichinose Chizuru
You there?
Please believe me. I'm telling the truth.
The one who loves Kazuya-kun
more than anyone else...
Add Friend
is... is m...
Oh, hello? Yeah, it's me.
I'll put her on.
G-Gran.
Itabashi Third Hospital
Hello, Grandmother?
I'm sorry for keeping you waiting.
It's Chizuru.
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Birthday
party
time!!
Mizuhara Chizuru.
You see, my grandma is a
little under the weather.
Um, can you hear me?
Oh, forgive me.
Your voice is just so lovely,
I was lost in it.
Is she your long-lost
granddaughter?
Her stare stings!
She's wondering why
I have her contact.
Chizuru-san
Kazuya, happy birthday!
Chizuru-san Love
Is Sayutaso all right?
Y-Yes. She isn't in any danger or anything.
It's fine, really. I totally understand.
We can always celebrate
your birthday another time.
Sayutaso comes first.
Here, Kazuya. Pass.
It's like she
just got out
of the bath.
Why does she look so content?!
Gonna step outside for a bit.
Sure. Tell my angel I said bye.
The absolute best timing possible!
Ichinose Chizuru
I never expected to get a call from her.
The call's
still going!!
Hello, Mizuhara? Yeah, I'm outside now.
You were a big help.
I see.
Her
voice
is
so
cute...
A-Are you sure you should've
called me from your phone?
Listen, don't get the wrong idea.
Everyone in that group has added each other.
And I couldn't
not call
If we were the only ones who didn't,
we'd stick out like a sore thumb.
Oh...
Y-Yeah.
How are you dealing?
Well, Ruka-chan's here.
Huh? Ruka-chan? That's bad news!
Yeah, kinda.
So I wish you'd come save the day...
I'm sorry. My grandma isn't doing too great.
And I want to be there for her.
Okay, you don't have to come.
I'll manage somehow.
Huh? Are you sure you'll be okay?
Yeah. Gran seems content
just hearing your voice.
Really? But...
Yes, really! Don't bother showing up!
Go ahead and enjoy your private time!
Wha?!
Don't just grab my phone!
Also, you're a rental girlfriend!
What are you thinking, exchanging contact
info with another girl's boyfriend?!
Anyway, his family loves me now,
so you're not needed anymore!
Shut up, Ruka-chan!
I'm gonna make Kazuya-kun
mine for real tonight!
Kinoshita Kazuya
LIVE Audio call ended
C-Come on...
That didn't sound "okay" at all!
gloom
There's no guarantee she won't blab
about the rental girlfriend thing.
Hey, Grandma?
I'm actually supposed to visit
Kazuya-san's family home tonight.
They're throwing a birthday
party for me, too.
So... uh...
Why didn't you say so sooner?
You shouldn't be here!
It'd be terribly rude if you
didn't attend that party!
What are you doing,
leaving Kazuya-kun all by himself?!
Wow,
so much energy!
B-But, Grandma, you...
I'm fine! I just recovered!
Talk about a silver bullet...
Anyway, I can come back anytime.
Call me if you need me.
Get going already!
If you don't make it in time,
I'll come back to haunt you!
Sheesh, Grandma.
Hearing the name "Kazuya-san"
was enough to lift her spirits.
But...
Why did I talk to her about it?
He even told me I didn't have to go.
You're the one I want!
It's gotta be you!
I must be stupid, too.
To this address, please.
Also, I'm in a little bit of a hurry.
Want some beer, Kazuya?
S-Sure.
So I press this "Add Friend" button?
That's right.
And then scan my QR code on your phone.
They're exchanging
LIVE addresses...
Like this?
Things have taken a very bad turn.
Grandmother, about what
I was saying earlier...
Th-There it is!
Oh?
Sorry I'm late.
Mizuhara?
Chizuru, my angel!
A Septuagenarian's
Happy Birthday Dive
Wha...
Is Sayuri-san okay?
When I told her about the party,
she practically chased me out.
That's my Sayutaso.
In that case, happy birthday!
You're just as beautiful aged twenty!
A sight for sore eyes!
Sorry.
That's my girl! You're so cute!
And thanks.
Heya, Ruka-chan.
Pat Pat
Sorry I'm late.
N-No biggie!
Like, you didn't even
have to come.
Man, why'd Chizuru-san show up?
Does she like Kazuya-kun after all?
I told her not to bother, and still...
But I've built up a cache, a rapport
with the family in the time so far.
Not even Chizuru-san can erase it all!
Over here, Chizuru-san.
You're the guest of honor.
Oh, before I take a seat...
May I pay my respects at the family altar?
Wha...
That thought didn't even cross my mind!
What the heck? The family altar?
O-Of course. Please go
say hi to my husband.
I didn't even think of it.
This way!
It's over here!
Are girlfriends supposed
to pay their respects?
Wow, such a pretty altar.
You can tell?
Aren't you glad to see her, honey?
She's Kazuya's girlfriend.
Mother...
I'm happy for you, Mom.
She's turning things around!
All my efforts will be reduced to nothing!
I was scared out of my wits back then.
Maybe you should get your act together, then.
This sake is really easy to drink.
Wow, you have good taste, Chizuru-san.
Oh, Chizuru-san, where do you live?
E-Er... Sakuradai...
Oho? You two live in the same neighborhood?
Have you considered living together, then?
Wha? L-L-Living together?!
I think you've had enough to drink, Gran!
Huh? She's gone?
I'm glad Ruka-chan didn't hear that!
I'd die if I lived together with Mizuhara...
It's my fault, really.
If I'm too close to Kazuya-san,
I lean on him too much.
And these days, women have
to be independent, too.
What a model answer.
Hear that, Kazuya?
It's you! You've got to get it together!
I need to use the restroom.
Mizuhara's shining so bright,
it's making my darkness stand out.
All this fantasy crap about living
together, getting married...
She's a rental girlfriend, damn it!
Gotta hand it to Mizuhara, though.
Everything she's doing is
professional to the extreme.
She's got Gran back to normal, too.
And she seemed like a ticking time bomb,
but Ruka-chan's calmed down
ever since Mizuhara got here.
Tears
of
relief
Oh, that's where you went.
Similar situation here.
S-Sorry, I need to go.
Oh, the tie?
Thanks...
A pendulum clock?
Such an antique piece. I love it.
I bought it with my husband
back when we opened the store.
Wow... It's such a pretty sound.
Mwahaha. She who dares wins, Chizuru-san.
Huh?
The sudden appearance of a new
challenger caught me off-guard,
but I'll win the Kazuya-kun Sweepstakes
Kinoshita Family Reversi Tournament!
Were you all playing Reversi before I came?
Wow, look at you playing dumb.
Is this another one of your
schemes to make a comeback?
Uh, what is Ruka-chan even talking about?
B-Beats me.
Anyway, next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Ring and...
...Girlfriend."
"Ring and Girlfriend"
The victor's ring will be mine!